A twenty-first century portrait.
Vox Lux is a drama, music film directed by Brady Corbet.
In 1999, teenage sisters Celeste and Eleanor survive a seismic, violent tragedy.
The sisters compose and perform a song about their experience, making something lovely and
cathartic out of catastrophe — while also catapulting Celeste to stardom.
By 2017, the now 31-year-old Celeste is mother to a teenage daughter of her own and struggling to navigate a
career fraught with scandals when another act of terrifying violence demands her attention.
Celeste Montgomery, played by Natalie Portman.
Young Celeste / Albertine, played by Raffey Cassidy.
Manager, played by Jude Law.
Eleanor "Ellie" Montgomery, played by Stacy Martin.
Josie, played by Jennifer Ehle.
Journalist, played by Christopher Abbott.
Vox Lux is a 2018 American musical drama film written and directed by
Brady Corbet, from a story by Corbet and Mona Fastvold.
The film stars Natalie Portman, Jude Law, Raffey
Cassidy, Stacy Martin and Jennifer Ehle.
Vox Lux had its world premiere at the 75th Venice International Film Festival on September
4, 2018, and was released in the United States on December 7, 2018, by Neon.
The film received generally favorable reviews from film critics,
and grossed $1.4 million on an $11 million budget.
The film explores themes of pop star, icon, school shooting, 1990s, 2000s.
The tone is dark and emotional.